But don't worry.
I'll give it a real shot.
Big Laundromat
Heya.
Hello.
M-Mizuhara! Why is she here?!
Th-This is unusual.
D-Did your machine break down?
I use this place
all the time
Bingo. I used to come here with
my grandma when I was little,
but it's a lot to carry around.
R-Right?
I feel you
W-Wait a second.
I'm being judged right now.
She might be picky
about enunciation
Does my voice sound cool?
This is a pop quiz!!
Did I walk here upright?!
Every single thing
gets me jumpy!!
Is my outfit passable?
I'm screwed
if my breath stinks!!
I should've brushed harder this morning!
Wait, why'd that shirt
have to be in front?!
Beef Tongue
with Salt
If she sees this,
I'll lose any chance I had!
Gotta hide it
It's too late
Okay, bye.
See you.
Close call.
She didn't look
at my bag
plump
Who dazzles like
this at 10 AM?!
Are you kidding me?
This is how she carries
herself at the laundromat?!
She's walking away from the machines
and still smells of softener!
Added, in fact
Sure, she's dressed casually,
but her hair's silky smooth!
You could start a photoshoot
here right now!
Wait a damn second!
She's always
had that?!
Where do they sell
such a cute laundry bag?!
Is everything
she has cute?!
She's a beauty in every aspect!
That's not her with no makeup, is it?
Her skin's even clearer than detergent!
Coin laundry owner, this is big news!
A customer
of legend
Just put up a pic of this
and you'll go viral
She makes people happier
wherever she goes.
Blessed
But every time I see her,
it chips away at my confidence.
Death by a thousand cuts
Stop that.
Don't be a pessimist!
For now, I should get rid
of this T-shirt!!
A girl like that considers me an option!
No need to wash it!
Be positive!
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Bra and Girlfriend"
Still there!
It's there, all right!
What now?! I mean,
Mizuhara's
underwear?!?!
the other machines are being used.
And this is totally a hot girl's bra!
There aren't that many
machines here anyway
She walked out from around here, too.
There's almost no doubt about it!
But wait, what do I do?
Should I go after Mizuhara?
How am I supposed to tell her
she left her bra behind, though?
And if I take it out and she finds out
I touched it, I'll get labeled a perv!
Hmm...
But hey, it is a lost item.
Right? Whatever it is, it's a lost item.
It's only natural to pick it up
and give it back to its owner!
There's probably a phone
number written somewhere
The
management's,
I mean
That way, she won't
find out that I found it
The eyes of a sex offender
Natural!
Perfectly natural!
Damn, this is lewd.
Hey.
lunge
Wait, what?! She's back?!
Did she realize? That was quick!
That she forgot
What are you doing? That's freaky.
So it was Mizuhara's
Wait, wait, timeout!
We're alone right now!
It's just me and the bra!
shove
dump
His own laundry
Wh-What's up? Did you forget something?
This is my only resort! It wasn't there!
I can't recover from sticking my
head in the washing machine,
but it's better than her finding out!
My laundry and Mizuhara's bra
sitting in a machine! K-I-S-S-I-N-G!
No, not really.
Sorry, but...
Just assume you lost it
and leave, Mizuhara!
Wait, she's staying here?
Well, duh! It's not easy
to ask if I saw her bra.
She's hoping to find it
without me finding out!
Was it her special underwear?!
She couldn't just leave it be
Aren't you going to run the machine?
Huh? Oh, right.
Yeah, I was going to.
I just like to let it sit for a bit.
What does that even mean?
My score just dropped with that!
Gah, my clothes and Mizuhara's
bra are swimming together!
Oh, the depravity!
Wait, she's still hanging around?
She's still not leaving?
What she lost
Just call it a lost cause at this point.
It can't be here now that
I've started my laundry.
If she waits until it's done, I'm toast!
She's acting strange, too.
I guess even Mizuhara would feel
bashful about losing her bra.
Silent
Has she seen thorough me
and realized I was lying?
wiggle wiggle
The countdown to my death
has already begun!
98 minutes left
Here.
Kinoshita-sama
Tickets to my upcoming play.
Tickets...?
I mean, I can't very well not
give you tickets at this point.
You've helped me
out a lot
Kinoshita-sama
Tickets! She did say it opens soon.
For me
Mizuhara!
I'll go!
I'll go for sure!
O-Okay.
See you.
That's all
S-Sure.
Wait, what? What about the bra?
It was just a ticket. Why couldn't
I just hand it to him and be done?
So stupid.
Oh, Kinoshita-san.
Have you seen my bra around here?
Without
realizing
I washed it again.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Storage Space
Thank you so much.
It's amazing that you made a whole movie.
That's not an experience many
college students get to have.
Oh, not at all.
I didn't do anything
The staff did everything.
Please bring your business
here again sometime
You have until the end of the month
for the money transfer.
I finished sending out all
the backer rewards today,
so I canceled our storage space!
With this, the entire
movie project is a wrap!
Thanks a ton!
Okay.
Send it
Karaoke Village
staaare
Stare.
wash wash
beam
What's up?
Oh, nothing at all.
Please continue
Y-Yeah?
You're staring awfully
hard for nothing
It's just, your complexion's
so much better now.
You were so down in the dumps for
a while. You even took days off work.
I was really worried, you know?
You were asleep every time I came over,
You wouldn't reply to
my LIVE messages, either
and I'd clean and clean,
but the place got messy in no time.
Yeah, I feel like she was
really doing a lot for me.
When I found out it was because
Chizuru-san was ghosting you,
of course it didn't feel good
as your girlfriend...
But honestly, it hurt a lot more
seeing you in that state.
cling
But... But now!
You'll get
wet!
Don't cling to me!
You'll get
yourself wet!
But if you've recovered to this extent,
that must mean you're over her now!
Doesn't sound like Chizuru-san
got back in touch with you
Huh? Wha... uh?
What was that?
Huwhauh?
Sorry about
all that
Nah, I'm just sorry for worrying you.
My boyfriend's finally escaped
the rental girlfriend's clutches,
and he's now looking at me alone!
Ack...
It's going to start!
Our very own story is about to begin!
How can I tell her I bounced back
because Mizuhara said she'd look into it?
How I've waited for this time to come!
I'm not telling her for a billion yen.
Rentn't-a-Girlfriend begins next episode!
Ichinose Chizuru
I told you I'd help. Did it go okay?
I got a reply from Mizuhara.
Is she on lunch break
or something...
Ichinose Chizuru
I think I'll go with blue for the outfit.
Sure, we texted while
we were making that movie.
But Mizuhara's replies were
always short and to the point.
Even that made
me happy
ba-dump
But now we have a question.
She's trying to keep the convo going.
And I can faintly feel
her concern and kindness.
She knows what I went through!
She must've made time to reply.
I hope I wasn't a bother.
She's a busy gal
Who is it?
Just spam.
Okay, let's go. Things sure
get busy over spring break.
Really?
I told you I'd help. Did it go okay?
Hey, it was my job!
It was fine! Thanks for asking!
I didn't get to see my angel
Chizuru once over the winter.
I missed seeing her in any
winter outfits because of that!
I'll die!
I'll die, you hear?!
It was one whole season
I'll haunt you
When my life flashes before my eyes,
Are you
flying, Gran?!
Ow!!
the last thing I see has to
be her in her Sunday best!
What kinda threat is that
After all that happened,
you'd better not tell me you broke up.
W-We're doing fine!
I talked my way out of it,
because there's no way I could tell her
she ghosted me for three whole months.
Not to Gran...
I need my supply!
From the official source!
I need my angel fix..!!
pant pant
Don't call it "fix"
Seriously, what is with your...
Ichinose Chizuru
Is there a storage facility nearby?
I told you I'd help. Did it go okay?
Hey, it was my job! It was fine! Thanks for asking!
Is there a storage facility nearby?
The one I used is in Takanodai!
If you're looking for a trunk room in Nerima-ku, Tokyo!
Here!
Chi-chan?
Why are you spacing out?
Sorry. I'm just a little sleep-deprived.
I bet you were poring
over the script until late.
You always do too much. It worries me.
Right back at you, Shi-chan.
Rehearsal's starting. Let's go.
Yeah.
Here!
Ichinose Chizuru
Wow, that's cheaper than I expected.
I have way too many clothes.
What's the place like?
It's really good!
The staff were nice and thorough, too!
Hey, son? Your order's ready.
Oh, sorry, I was zoning out.
Is it hard managing all your outfits?
If you don't control the humidity,
they go bad quickly. A lot of my
friends throw them away, but I
was hesitant to, and now they
don't fit in my closet
I'm torn between this and Rental Pocket
Yeah, humidity's gotta
be hard to deal with
Rental Pocket! I looked it up when starting
the crowdfunding project! But I chose this one because
I might have needed some of the stuff on short notice
Ichinose Chizuru
If you don't control the humidity, they go bad quickly.
How quickly do they go bad?
Half a year or so? Rainy season's particularly bad.
Now I have two years' worth of winter outfits
That's a lot
Rental Pocket might be the choice for
winter outfit storage
Rental Pocket might be the choice for winter outfit storage
Ichinose Chizuru
I thought so, too.
Thanks for filling me in, though
Thanks for filling me in, though.
Anytime! I've looked into a fair few things,
so I'll answer anything I can!
I'm really grateful you made that movie.
Thank you again.
Don't mention it! I only did what I could!
Couldn't have done it without you all
What was the hardest part?
Tell us, Producer
Is this an interview? lol
It was a lot of fun! None of it was "hard."
If I had to say, though...
All those calls to secure the crew's schedule,
running around Tokyo to secure equipment,
and getting inflammation from all the
reward packing...
So much for "none of it." lol
Great work, seriously.
It was a wonderful experience for me, too.
Nothing makes me happier!
Thanks for the play ticket!
I'll go see it for sure!
Thanks. It got delayed once
and things got chaotic, so
I'm glad it's finally opening
Really? Sounds rough
The crew did a lot behind the scenes.
I'm fine! We performers only have to
do our best onstage!
Burning with Passion
Can we not with those stickers...
Sorry, sorry
I really did gift those by mistake...
It happens
It does?
Did it weird you out when you got it?
It didn't weird me out,
but I was kinda confused
Oh God LOL
Who needs those, right? Came outta nowhere, too
Oh, but Yoko does use these, rarely
Really? That's a surprise
About twice in two years
That IS rare
Why did Yoko-chan even buy them? lol
Don't ask me lol
We're gonna be third-years soon!
Right?
Is there a job-hunting process for acting?
Not like for everyone else
Every project is a job hunt, I guess?
Oh, that's how it works?
Will you take over the store
as soon as you graduate?
I'm rooting for you!
Crap, replied to the wrong thing, sorry
No need to apologize lol
Ichinose Chizuru
Will you take over the store
as soon as you graduate?
I'm still thinking. I feel like it'd be
important to get a job and
build experience.
I'm talking to my family about it!
Wow, that's admirable of you
Do you have a field in mind?
Cowwunications? Maybe finance?
Typo
Way to go, me
Is that, like, communicating with cows?
It's okay, you don't have to keep it going
lol
Do you have any companies in mind?
Honestly, I have no clue
I mean, it'd be nice to work for
a famous corporation...
This is Nerima U
It's Nerima U all right
lolol
Hey, jinx! lol
Sorry, Nerima U
I guess a talent agency would be your
"workplace"?
We do sign with one,
but it's closer to freelancing
Freelancing! That's so cool
It's not. Everyone says it's feast or famine
But I know you'll do great!!
Cheers, buddy
You're making fun of me, aren't you...?
Don't worry about it, mate
Tomorrow's a new day, comrade
Rawwwr!
These might be surprisingly versatile lol
Thanks for them
Glad to hear it lol
Hmm?
Wha? It's that late?
Talk about a time sink!
I mean, I've never gotten so many
replies from Mizuhara before!
We had such a natural convo!
Squee! I hope she's not wondering
when this will end!
Would a smooth guy say
goodnight here and let her sleep?
Her texts read like she
was having fun, though
The second most difficult thing ever is
knowing when to stop texting your crush.
But honestly, I wish it'd keep going
tomorrow and the day after.
If I stop here, who knows
when it'll start again...
What category is that?
Hmm?
Ack! She hasn't replied for ten minutes!
See what I mean?!
Two messages ago would've
been a good place to stop!!
I guess I was being a bother!
I used her feeling-out process as an
excuse to bombard her with messages!
I messed up!!
Forgive me
I'm sorry, Mizuhara! I'm really sorry!
Come back!!
Come back to the chat!!
Yep, it's all over.
I can't...
No response for two hours.
Needy...
She's going to ghost me
for three months again.
April 7
I'll give it a real shot.
mumble
Mizuhara...
It was now the spring of
my third year in college.
Wait, Ichinose?! Our Ichinose?!
Come to think of it
When I heard the name,
I did wonder if it was Yokko's friend.
Yoko (Yokko)
Sasano's girlfriend
Sorry about that
Wait, wait, wait! Wait a sec!
So that was Chizuru-san at our boozer?
And you were hiding it from us?!
Sounds like it.
Oh, yeah! She was there
on that beach trip, too!
What is with your nerves
(acting ability)?!
That's so scary! It's basically horror!
How can real life be so movie-like?!
You only realized
now, Kuri?
I-It just happened to turn out that way.
It was all Mizuhara...
Hang on.
I can't
overlook this
Does that mean Yokko still doesn't know?
A masked friend?
Oh, nah, I think that's
her true self, anyway.
She's not tricking her friends.
Huh... I guess it's okay, then.
It's gonna be hard to keep
all this from her, though.
She's my girlfriend
I-I'll ask about it.
Ask Chizuru!
ASAP, pls.
It's become such a big deal that it's
gonna be hard ironing out the wrinkles.
It's quite the
predicament
My bad, Kuri
The ripples
How should I face her if
I run into her on campus?
We're third-years, huh?
Things will start to change.
Eh, lots of people work in secret.
Just be normal, man.
Sasa-pai's
a fourth-year now
I gotta make sure I don't
cause any more problems.
I dunno if I can without
thinking about it.
Yo.
Heya, Kibe.
Whatcha talking about?
Just about how Chizuru-san's
actually the Ichinose from Literature.
Oh, yeah, right.
Wait, you knew?!
How could you not put it together
after hearing her name?
What are you,
an ace detective?
Heya, Kazu-chin.
H-Hey.
Kibe...
Apparently, avocados can
heal erectile dysfunction.
It's been four months.
We're interacting normally,
Where'd that come from?
but it feels like we're both
trying to avoid the topic.
We're gonna swing by the club room.
It's kinda awkward.
See ya.
Bye.
Now we're alone!
What do you have next, Kazu-chin?
O-Organizational Management Theory.
We can head to B Wing together, then.
Y-Yeah.
But it makes sense, given what came out.
Just apologizing in front of everyone
won't make things go back to normal.
He's one of the people
I made look bad the most.
He didn't show up for dinner
after that at Hawaiians, either.
He probably feels like
I betrayed his trust.
Watching you does make me feel like
I want to be friends with believers.
So what's all this, you little punk?!
There's no going back for us anymore.
I'm sorry, Kibe!
I'm sorry for lying about
Chizuru for so long!
I tried to tell you so many times,
but I didn't have the strength.
And look what it led to.
I swear, I wasn't trying
to trick you or anything!
I'm not holding a grudge over
something from four months ago.
I have better things to do.
Awkward guys get called that 'cause they
can't handle too many things at once.
Of course, some do hit the big time
and gain money and influence,
but most people try to protect
what's dear to them as best they can.
To be honest, it hurt when I thought
you were lying to me the whole time.
Sure, I was jealous of you walking
around with a hottie like that,
but mostly I was happy for you,
and I thought you two were a good match.
I also believed that our talks had gone
past "frank" into "crude" territory.
And I felt ridiculous for not even
searching "Mizuhara Chizuru" online.
But she's your girlfriend now, right?
That must mean you share a special bond.
When I figured she's more important to
you than I am, everything fell into place.
Kibe...
Hey, everyone lies for
the things they care about.
It doesn't mean they do it out of malice.
I was just wrong about how incapable
I thought you were of lying.
It doesn't mean I don't still
consider you a good guy.
Now, all I think is I'll take a chainsaw
to your guts if you ever break up.
Relax. I'll crush your skull,
even if I become a zombie.
Man, I don't wanna go to class.
I see...
He feels that way, even though
I did him dirty by lying?
Kibe!
Y-You're not serious, are you?
I'll press your balls into a bookmark.
Bookmark?
Formalin's not cheap, y'know.
I think it can wait until after you've
come to terms with your own feelings.
You're such a bro, Kibe!
BFFs forever
Seriously, anybody but him
would've cut ties with me.
But I'm still lying
about us being a couple.
I haven't made it up to him yet.
If that gets out, he'll be well
within his rights to skewer me alive.
Yeah, not yet.
I'm going to look into it.
I'll give it a real shot.
We're on the way!
Breaking
Ruins Excavation in Barcelona
Regarding the excavation
project in Barcelona,
the survey team on the scene...
Are we really on the way?!
Mizuhara hasn't gotten
in touch for a week now.
She did say she had no idea
What if she's stuck right after
she started her investigation?!
how to go about it!!
Or maybe she has her answer already!
I looked into it more,
and you get 1 point.
It went down
boing                       boing
Gah, I'm so worried!
Fish on the
cutting board
So much so that I might
just send her a
LIVE message asking wyd?
More worried and terrified
than I've ever been!
I wonder if Yaemori-san's in.
I'll go talk to her...
Mizuhara!
You startled me.
She was about to
ring my doorbell?!
S-Sorry.
Were you about to head out?
Nah, just airing the place out.
I wanted a taste of the fresh spring air.
Our windows are pretty tiny
This is the problem
with run-down apartments
So you're free, then?
Yeah, what's up?
Mizuhara?! What does she want?!
I wanted you to come over for a bit.
Huh?
What?!
What cute wallpaper.
Where's the bedroom?
This is way beyond "investigation"!
You're making me blush. I love you.
Come over?!
Are you sure you want it to be so sudden?!
I'm not ready for this
I get that you need to check,
but it's too soon for this!
I mean, I'll go...
Wh-What's wrong? Do you have a leak?
butt
Wait, no. When I say
"come over," I mean...
to my grandma's place.
Wha?
I'm so glad my Kazuya
got back on his feet!
Sorry for making you worry.
You should be! As punishment,
heal my heart and soul!
Hug!
Hey, stop that! We're on the clock!
Get away from me!
Oh, no more, Kazuya!
We'll get kicked off the air!
I'm not doing anything, okay?!
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Childhood Home and...
...Girlfriend."
We're talking about a home
and raising a child?
"Childhood Home and Girlfriend"
Hold your horses, Kazuya!